http://www.aultman.com/privacy-policy

Careers
330-452-9911 (Aultman Main)
Schedule an Appointment
*Please fill in all the required fields.
Your form has been submitted. Thank you!
Do you have an order from a physician and want to schedule an appointment?
Aultman Wait Times
Choose Immediate Care for colds/flu, sprains/strains and other minor injury/illness.
Go to the ER for major concerns and trauma. Call 911 for chest pain and stroke symptoms.
Location Finder
Here's your guide to finding any of the facilities in the Aultman family of health services, including maps and contacts.
Need a Doctor?
Aultman Medical Group's network of more than 240 providers is committed to high-level patient care.
Schedule an Appointment
Call 330-363-6288 or click below to complete an online form.
Donate Today
You can help support and enhance services, and in turn, help patients and their families who benefit from care received at Aultman.
Website Privacy Policy
We maintain high standards for the protection of your privacy when you use our website. The disclaimers described below explain how we collect and use your personal information, what you can expect from our website, and the steps that we take to protect your personal information. Your use of this website is subject to the terms and conditions contained in our policies and disclaimers.Your InformationWe do not collect your personal identifying information when you access this website unless:
You register to use the services offered on our website; or
You provide information to us in an e-mail.
To register and use the password-protected services offered on this website, we collect the following information from you: First and last name, Insurance Member identification number, date of birth, company or employer name, and e-mail address. You will also be asked to create a username, password, and reminder question with answer. All information provided by you to us will be used strictly for permitting you to use our website, for responding to your questions, for maintaining the functionality of our website, and for protecting the security of your personal information. We will store all information that you provide to us in a manner that protects the privacy and security of your personal information. We are committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information and we will not sell, transfer, or disclose your personal information, including your e-mail address, without your prior authorization, except when permitted or required by law.E-mailYou may send an e-mail directly to us using the links provided on this website. If you provide your e-mail address, we may reply to you by e-mail. All information that you share with us will be kept confidential in accordance with our policies and procedures. Depending upon the nature of your e-mail, we may dispose of your e-mail correspondence or retain it after we reply to you. Please note that certain e-mail applications may not provide full encryption or security during transfer to us. Therefore, please contact our Service Center by telephone if your question contains any information that you consider to be confidential. Telephone numbers are listed under the Contact Us section.CookiesWe use cookies on both the public access and password-protected areas of this website. A “cookie” is a piece of data that transfers to your computer when you visit or access a website. Cookies do not collect personal information from you. We use cookies to make this website easier for you to access by customizing certain functions, such as saving usernames and passwords. Cookies also help us to improve our website by providing information on use of the website, as well as functionality of the website.Terms and Conditions for Use of our WebsiteThis website is owned and operated by Aultman Health Foundation for the use of its patients, visitors, staff, providers, and other interested users. We reserve the right to alter or discontinue any aspect or feature of this site without notice and at our sole discretion. We retain the right, but not the duty, to monitor this site for any and all purposes. Any monitoring of this website will be conducted in compliance with all applicable privacy regulations. You agree to use this website only in the manner for which it was intended. Certain functions of this site are available only to authorized users with prior security clearance. You expressly agree to use this website at your own risk. Neither the company, nor its employees, officers, agents, business partners, or affiliated institutions, is liable in any way for any errors, omissions, interruptions, deletions, defects, delays in transmission, computer virus, etc., that may result from the use of this site. We strive to maintain this site in an accurate and current manner; however, we do not guarantee the accuracy of any information, service, or merchandise provided through this site. This website may contain links to other Internet websites that are provided solely for your convenience or interest. We make no warranties or representations as to the content of any website accessed through these links, and assume no liability or responsibility for the accuracy, legality, or decency of any site you may access through the website. Similarly, if you have accessed this website as a link provided by another Internet site, this in no way or manner indicates any endorsement, approval, association, obligation, responsibility or liability of, by or for, Aultman Health Foundation and the operator of the website providing the link. This disclaimer applies to any damages or injury caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, delay of transmission, etc., whether for breach of contract, tortious behavior (including strict liability), negligence, or any other cause of action. Neither the company, nor any person or entity involved in creating or producing this website, or the content herein, is liable in contract, tort, or any other legal theory of liability for any economic or non-economic damages, including but not limited to, direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive, consequential, or similar damages, arising out of the use or an inability to use this website. The terms and conditions of this website are governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Ohio. Any action related to matters on this website shall be brought in state court in Stark County, Ohio or in federal court in the United States District Court, Northern District of Ohio.
Location Finder
Here's your guide to finding any of the facilities in the Aultman family of health services, including maps and contacts.
Need a Doctor?
Aultman Medical Group's network of more than 240 providers is committed to high-level patient care.
Schedule an Appointment
Call 330-363-6288 or click below to complete an online form.
Donate Today
You can help support and enhance services, and in turn, help patients and their families who benefit from care received at Aultman.
2600 Sixth St. S.W. in Canton, OH 44710    |    330-452-9911
